嗨 Dan，我们完成设置了，你要检查看看吗？
Hey Dan, we finished the settings. Do you want to check it out?
恩 很好
>> Oh, great.
等等，这里这些是什么鬼？
>> Wait. What's with all this stuff right here?
很高兴你问了。这些是用来演示
>> I'm glad you asked. All this stuff will help me demonstrate the
implicit intents的作用的
power of implicit intents. Leveraging other
借助其他APP来实现你的APP的功能
apps to get functionality for your app
举个例子，如果你可以通过一个intent来扫描条形码，
for free. For example, why would you write a bar code scanning app,
你干嘛还要自己编写一个扫描条形码的程序
when you can just launch an intent to do it for you. [SOUND].
再例如你可以通过intent来照一张照片而不需要编写一个相机APP
>> Or a camera app, where you can just launch
当然，也没有必要单独编写一个电话APP仅仅用来拨号
an intent to fire a photo. [SOUND] And of course, it would make no sense to
你只需要调用一个intent就可以了
write a phone app just to dial a phone number, you would just call the intent.
等 这个我要
>> Wait, I need that.
所以不要做别人做过的事情，越懒的码农犯错越少
>> In other words, don't reinvent the wheel. Lazy programmers make fewer
好了，现在我们来编写一个implicit intent吧
mistakes. Now, let's go implement an
Raydo? Dan又变得implicit了
implicit intent. Raydo? Dan's being implicit again.